I will not allow this.
You perverted kidnapper.
Anya is too young to get married!
Even I, only got married this year!
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
-Anya was so scared!
-It's okay. Everything's all right now.
That's her mother?
Damn it.
I'll have to get rid of both of them.
All right dogs, go and sink your teeth
into that woman's windpipe!
Hey!
Mother! I'm so scared!
Everything's all right!
-What's going on?
-Is it a fight?
Damn it. I can't stay here any longer.
Come here, you big mutt! You bastard!
You're no use!
Stop right now!
No, Yor, you can't leave Anya alone again.
I'm sure this kidnapper
has learned his lesson.
In the meantime, I have to turn this man
over to the police.
Doggie, are you okay?
Where did that dog come from?
Um…
What? Terrorists and bomb dogs?!
A bomb?
A bomb…
There's none here.
This doggie saved Anya's life.
I'm just glad you were safe, Anya.
I was so worried.
I'm sorry for going outside on my own.
As you should be.
You're getting a lecture once we get home.
Either way, we must report this
to the police right away.
Anya, do you remember what those
bad guys looked like,
and what they were talking about?
Um… I'll try hard to remember.
…So that's the whole story.
Yes, there's one person here
who is unconscious.
No, I'm just a housewife
that happened to be passing by.
Doggie…
You're seeing the future again.
Father is gone!
Where is this?
Father!
Westalis is strongly criticizing
the Ostanian government
regarding the Minister's assassination,
and military conflict between
west and east seems inevitable.
What I saw right now is the future?
The future is a shambles!
Father is dead and there's no peace!
Stop it, Anya. Be nice to the dog.
…Oh, sorry. Yes, and then…
Father will get killed with a bomb…
I'll tell Mother and have her help us.
But I can't tell her about
my supernatural power.
Doggie,
is it possible to change the future?
Can you still run?
Mother, I'm sorry. I remembered…
That Father didn't take toilet paper
to the bathroom!
-What?
-He's probably in a pinch right now,
so I'm going to take him
some toilet paper!
Wait, Anya!
Where did she run off to now?
Sorry. Anyway, please arrest
those criminals.
Excuse me…
Anya!
Anya! Where are you?
Handler.
We intercepted a call made from
the alleyway near central station,
reporting a terrorist sighting.
The description and story
matches that of the university students.
They're on the move.
Position the team on predicted routes
from that scene.
Stop all white vans that
match our description.
They might be carrying explosives,
so be cautious.
Oh…
Why…
Team Alpha has captured
four members and three dogs.
We also found a case
with possible explosives.
This is Bravo. We also captured
three members.
The leader, Keith Kepler, is not here.
We'll keep searching this area.
They got us! Are they the Secret Police?
Or the bastards from the west?
What should I do? There's only two hours
until the summit begins.
There's one more location
where the explosives are hidden.
I'll have to do it.
Even if I have to do it on my own.
Spill it! Where's the ambush location,
and Keith's whereabouts?
The answer is, "Kiss my ass!"
Go stick your head in the toilet,
you corrupted pigs!
Crush those pigs in the west!
Crush them!
You little brat.
We have enough barking with the dogs.
So shut up.
Hey, university kids.
What is it that you guys want?
It's war! We want to remove
all the countries in the west,
and make Ostania the supreme--
Have you guys ever killed anyone before?
Or have you guys ever been killed before?
Of course not, you idiot!
Have your arms or legs ever been
torn apart by firearms?
Have you ever heard the sound
of bones being crushed?
Or smelled the scent of festering flesh?
What are you saying, you old hag!
Have you ever seen your family getting
crushed inside a collapsing house?
Have you ever seen pieces of
your lover's flesh plastered on the wall?
Have you ever been so hungry
that you had to eat tree bark?
Have you ever cooked human flesh in a pot?
Do you have anyone close to you,
who dehumanized their enemies
and continued killing them,
only to suffer emotional damage
after being discharged,
causing themselves to shed tears
of regret and shame, while throwing up,
and finally killing themselves?
It seems like you didn't learn anything
about war while attending university…
…little boys and girls.
Listen up. Once you confirm
the Minister's scent,
don't let him get away.
I'm leaving it up to you, doggo.
But,
now that everyone's caught,
plan B's hideout might have been leaked.
Then I can't use any of the locations near
the clock tower because of the security.
In that case, I'll trap and get rid of
those people who are trying to stop me.
Just watch, you pigs.
I'll blow you all away.
All teams. Conduct a search
from point B1 to B4.
Twilight, I want you to go to B1,
the area with the highest probability.
Make sure to put a stop to this.
I understand, Handler.
I feel the same way as you.
I'm sick and tired of war.
I found the clock tower!
That way, Doggie!
That's where Father will die!
I have to stop him!
Here in Central Berlint,
traffic is being controlled
in preparation for the summit,
and the media is limited as well
due to tight security.
We finally made it to the clock tower.
Where is Father going to die?
Doggie, show me that image once again!
I think the clock went "gong"
when the bomb exploded!
It was when the hands were pointing up!
That means the amount of time
we have left is…
Anya doesn't know how to read the clock!
The short hand and the long hand.
Which is what?
Excuse me.
How many minutes until that clock
goes "gong"?
Oh, you mean the bell?
It rings every hour,
so there's 30 minutes
until it rings again.
Thanks a bunch.
Thirty minutes! I have to hurry!
Hm? How many minutes is 30 minutes?
What?
What's wrong, Doggie?
It's the leader of the bad guys!
Hey! Don't get out of the car!
Did he find us?
Hurry up and get back in the car,
you dumb mutt! I'm in a hurry!
I have to hurry up and get out of here,
or those guys will find me.
You better go off just as I planned.
I'm counting on you…
my impromptu trap!
The bomb explosion is his fault?
Come after me, you bastards.
The moment you enter the hideout,
it'll explode.
That building…
Some civilians might be sacrificed
when the bomb explodes,
but it can't be helped.
It's for a great cause.
Well, I'm sure you'll be satisfied
if you can die for your own country.
This is a crisis! We have to do something
about that bomb!
The hand on the clock went from
six to seven…
So there's seven minutes left?
Um… Either way, let's hurry!
Is this it?
Oh that's right! It's going to explode
the moment I open it!
I think I can go in
through that small window.
Give me a push, Doggie!
It's the bomb!
If I can defuse this,
Father will be saved!
How do I defuse it?
On TV shows,
bombs were defused by choosing
the red or blue wire. Where's the wire?
Where's the wire?
What?! All the wires are black!
More importantly, there are no scissors
to cut the wires with!
What should I do? I'm running out of time.
When Father gets here,
should I tell him not to come in?
Then my secret will come out
and I might get abandoned again.
But if Father dies,
both Anya and peace will be in a pinch.
That's point B1?
It's the room in the north
on the third floor.
Hurry. We don't have much time.
What is that? Is it written in blood?
No, it smells like ketchup.
There's an eggplant and grass drawn on
the door. Is it a new code?
I don't sense anyone here,
but let's be cautious.
No, we can't afford that kind of time.
The Minister will be leaving soon.
We can't let one university student
make us fall behind.
Father, did you notice my "dying message"?
It's too far to read his mind.
Father, are you okay?
I think…
this is the time I saw in the future…
The bomb…
didn't go off!
We did it!
Father is back!
We saved the future!
I have a bad feeling.
This might be a message.
We mustn't let our guard down.
Just as I thought. It's a trap.
It will go off once the door opens.
That means this is a bomb,
and not an eggplant?
That was close.
It seems like he knew we were
going to come here.
But who wrote this warning?
We don't have time to investigate.
People from the state security are here.
Let's leave them a warning statement
and let them defuse the bomb.
It's best for us to leave this area.
In the end, we weren't able to find Keith.
It's hard for us to investigate
with the state police on the watch.
Let's head to where the Minister is.
Now that his plan has failed,
the culprit might make an all-out attack
in a desperate attempt.
Minister Brantz, it's time.
Please head over to the reception hall.
Ostania's foreign affairs personnel
is there.
The government is always keeping watch
in this country.
I'm sure it's because of the issue
regarding the terrorist attack.
WISE hasn't gotten rid of the culprit yet?
What useless fools.
Excuse me.
I'm from the intelligence agency.
Minister, we will be leading the way
in our car.
The car is ready, Minister.
No, I will drive on my own.
Um…
All of you guys may leave.
Minister!
He's not close enough for me to see.
It's just as I guessed.
He's relying on the dog to trace my scent.
What's going on, Sylvia!
One of your men came by,
and he suddenly robbed me!
I'm borrowing your clothes.
What?
What a rude man!
I'm sorry, Minister.
But it was quite an emergency.
I think he needed to use your scent,
to confuse the dogs.
Right now the enemy is
a few kilometers away following the decoy.
You should head out now.
Oh, and please put on some clothes
to maintain our country's dignity.
Minister!
He changed route?
He changed route again?
What's going on?
We've been going around in circles!
I've identified it. It's a gray coupe.
From what I saw, there's only one dog.
Let's corner him. Lead him to Blue Four.
What? He's returning to the hotel?
No he's heading towards the lake,
to the deserted area.
That works for me!
Damn it!
Whoa! Back up!
He got us!
He still had some explosives left.
Be careful. He's headed your way.
Where did he go?
There he is!
That moron got out of the car
of his own free will.
Go!
The moment that dog gets hold of him,
I'm going to detonate that bomb.
Don't think you can run away
from a trained dog.
What? The Minister of the west is amazing!
That man is 60 years old!
Damn it! I'm going to lose him!
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you guys didn't want to be
involved in this senseless fight
between humans.
Let's end this.
MISSION: 15
A NEW FAMILY MEMBER
Subtitle translation by: